## Jaskaran Dhillon . Jarvis Consulting

A recent Computer Engineering graduate from McMaster University with a passion for software development. Experienced in full-stack development, having worked for 1.7 years in internships using technologies such as React, TypeScript, Spring Boot, and PostgreSQL. Being able to solve real-world complex problems drives me to keep improving my craft in this industry, always seeking the next greater challenge.

#### Skills

Proficient: Java, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, React, ExpressJS, Agile/Scrum

Competent: Linux/Bash, Spring Boot, TypeScript, Linux, Jest, Git

Familiar: Docker, MongoDB, Python, fermentum, fermentum

### **Jarvis Projects**

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis\_data\_eng\_JaskaranDhillon

Cluster Monitor [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

## Core Java Apps [GitHub]:

- Twitter App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.
- JDBC App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.
- Grep App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.

Springboot App [GitHub]: Not Started

Python Data Analytics [GitHub]: Not Started

Hadoop [GitHub]: Not StartedSpark [GitHub]: Not Started

Cloud/DevOps [GitHub]: Not Started

#### Highlighted Projects

Web app for resturant [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Machine Learning: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

#### Professional Experiences

Software Developer, Jarvis (June 2024-present): Developing applications using Sprint Boot, Java, Linux, Docker.

Software Engineer Intern, Canada Life (May 2023 - August 2023): Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque

Software Engineer Intern, Sera4 (May 2021 - August 2022): Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque

#### Education

McMaster University (2018-2024), Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Engineering

# Miscellaneous

- Udacity Machine Learning (2019)
- Winner
- Soccer player